allyoucanbooks.com 2019-04-28

# ALL YOU CAN BOOKS PRIVACY POLICY | All You Can Books | AllYouCanBooks.com

We at All You Can Books, LLC (AYCB) recognize the importance of protecting your personal information and are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Because AYCB understands that you are concerned about privacy, we have instituted policies and security measures intended to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe and responsible manner. We also post this privacy policy so that you can agree to the kind of information we collect, how it is handled, and with whom it may be shared. Please read this privacy statement carefully. Our privacy policy covers the collection and use of certain information that may be collected by AYCB anytime you interact with AYCB, such as when you purchase a AYCB product or contact a technical support or sales associate. 

**BY ACCESSING OR USING THIS AYCB WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS AYCB PRIVACY STATEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, YOU MUST NOT ACCESS OR USE THIS SITE.**

The information we collect is used primarily to process orders. We never offer, sell, rent, or otherwise make available any user-provided information to third parties. You will never have to worry about receiving unsolicited email from third parties after ordering from us. 

To help ensure your privacy, we use the most up-to-date encryption technology to keep your personal information secure. Click the VeriSign and McAfee Secure icons on website to verify. 

**Collection of Personal Information**

When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as placing order, signing up for trial, downloading content, or obtaining technical support, AYCB may ask you to provide certain information by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, AYCB may require that you provide certain personal information, such as your name, title, company, mailing or billing or shipping address, e-mail address, phone number and other personal identifying information. In addition, when placing an order on the site, you may be asked to provide credit card or other payment information which we may keep or store on our servers.

**Security**

When you submit sensitive information via the AYCB website, your information is protected both online and off-line. Where personal or sensitive information is required, the AYCB website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption - the highest level of encryption available - to transmit this data. All information will be encrypted upon submission. This is done to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of the information you have submitted. While AYCB strives to protect the personal information you submit to us, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. Therefore, AYCB cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once your information has been received by AYCB, we will make our best effort to ensure its safety and security on our systems. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. At times, AYCB may hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf. These companies will only be provided the information they need to perform the service, and they are strictly prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Finally, while we will make every effort to preserve the privacy of our users, at times we may be required by law to disclose personal information. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

**Data Collection**

AYCB collects limited non-personally identifying information that your browser makes available when you visit our website. This log information includes but not limited to your Internet Protocol address, software and hardware attributes, your page history and in some cases, one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.

**Cookies**

To enhance your experience with our site, some of our web pages use cookies. Cookies are small text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. You can choose, with your browser, to not accept cookies. However, if you choose not to accept cookies, you may not be able to view all areas of our website.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

As we continue to develop our website and take advantage of technologies to improve the service we provide, this policy may change. If this policy does change, we will post the changes here. In addition, if we materially change any of our practices related to the collection and use of personal information, we will either notify users via e-mail or by posting notice on our website. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy and how we are protecting the personal information we collect.

**Questions**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or AYCB's adherence to this privacy statement, you can contact AYCB at [info@allyoucanbooks.com](mailto:info@allyoucanbooks.com).
